(Raj:)How's that Hater-ade
taste, bro?
(Raj:)Hey, this isn't
the way to work.
(Howard:)I just want to pop in
and make sure Ma's okay.
(Raj:)I thought Stuart
was looking after her.
(Howard:)He was, but now that her cast
is off, he moved out.
(Howard:)And honestly, I'm kind of glad.
(Howard:)It was getting a little weird.
(Raj:)How so?
(Howard:)I don't know,
they're...
(Howard:)chummy.
(Raj:)Like us?
(Howard:)No, not like us.
(Howard:)Creepy chummy,
(Howard:)like you and your dog.
(Raj:)She feeds him out
of her own mouth?
(Howard:)I mean, he calls
her Debbie,
(Howard:)she calls
him Stewie
(Howard:)and they're all giggly
around each other.
(Howard:)And believe me,
when food goes in that mouth,
(Howard:)it does not come out.
(Raj:)So are you worried
(Raj:)because he's replacing you
as a son
(Raj:)or are you worried because
he's becoming her lover?
(Howard:)First of all, no one can
replace me as a son.
(Howard:)I'm her little matzo ball.
(Howard:)And secondly,
(Howard:)my mother is well past
(Howard:)having any kind of sex life.